Guide to the Frank Fragale Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Recordings
  - Lipona for woodwind quintet. Memoirs du luc, 1 of 2, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Lipona for woodwind quintet. Memoirs du luc, 2 of 2, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Danza Drammatica for flute and piano, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Radio program, Standard Hour. Fantasia for cello and orchestra Parts 1 and 3 of 4Feb. 24, 1946, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Radio program, Standard Hour. Fantasia for cello and orchestra Parts 2 and 4 of 4Feb. 24, 1946, Instantaneous disc: 78 rpm, lacquer; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 55)